<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-05-01T21:12:46-07:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Tyler Argo</title><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html">I Have a Blog Now!</title><link href="/2017/04/30/i-have-a-blog-now.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Have a Blog Now!" /><published>2017-04-30T05:46:27-07:00</published><updated>2017-04-30T05:46:27-07:00</updated><id>/2017/04/30/i-have-a-blog-now</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/04/30/i-have-a-blog-now.html">&lt;p&gt;Wow, an actual blog. It’s been three years since I updated this site. Three years is a long time in
internet years! Why update now? Well, I’ve been meaning to update for a couple
of months now after a co-worker shared a link to my website in an email and I
felt the familiar shame and embarrassment of looking at code I wrote before
I knew any better. But what really sealed the
deal for me that it was time to update was the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.may1reboot.com/#/&quot;&gt;May1Reboot&lt;/a&gt; project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea is simple:
set a deadline for everyone who wants to participate to update their website
or portfolio. I think it’s exactly the kind of motivation I needed (that and my
hosting credits on my old hosting provider are going to run out &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/argo_49/status/846388186188177409&quot;&gt;on the same day&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what I’ll be writing about or how often I’ll be posting, but I feel
like it’s important for a professional software developer to have a blog for three
reasons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Knowledge sharing
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Make the things you’ve learned available to others&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Helping people!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Demonstrating your ability to communicate
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Make the things you’ve learned available to others in a way that doesn’t make
 the reader confused or fall asleep!&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;This is also important to show potential employers that you’re competent and
 can clearly explain a complex topic&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Knowledge crystalization
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Ok I just made that word up, but people say that one of the best ways to learn
 and retain information is to break it down and teach it to someone else&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll probably write about new things I learn about playing around with React,
Redux, GraphQL and all those things. I’m also relatively new to the Android ecosystem
so writing about Android-related topics from a web developer’s point of view
would also be useful to me and hopefully to someone else!
I might also toss in a few off-topic posts every once in a while
on something that isn’t related to software. I’ll try to keep the bar on
quality relatively low so I don’t get bogged down by the pressure of writing
extremely high quality content, but at the same time I want the technical pieces
I write to be correct and the non-technical pieces to be entertaining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s to yet another new blog on the internet!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Wow, an actual blog. It’s been three years since I updated this site. Three years is a long time in internet years! Why update now? Well, I’ve been meaning to update for a couple of months now after a co-worker shared a link to my website in an email and I felt the familiar shame and embarrassment of looking at code I wrote before I knew any better. But what really sealed the deal for me that it was time to update was the May1Reboot project.</summary></entry></feed>